MARCUS SIMON DASHE

Full-Stack Web and Mobile App Developer

400 Gbazango Kubwa NYSC Street, FCT Abuja marcusdashe.developer@gmail.com | (+234)803 4477 604

PROFILE SUMMARY

Highly proficient and motivated software engineer with over 5 years of experience in the full software development cycle. I have developed and maintained scalable, reliable and efficient software systems. My objective is to add value by solving problems creatively to an organization and motivated to advance and expand my skill set through challenging projects.

CORE COMPETENCY

- Java/Kotlin, Springboot, Jetpack Compose, Android
- Dart/Flutter
- JavaScript/Typescript, Node.js, Express.js, React.js/Next.js
- HTML, CSS/TailwindCSS
- Solidity, Ether.js, Hardhat, IPFS
- Python, FastAPI
- PostgresSQL, MariaDB, MongoDB
- Docker, Bash Scripting, Git/GitHub

INTEREST

- Web Development
- Mobile App Development
- RESTful API and Web Services
- Blockchain and Cryptocurrency

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

C-STEMP LTD/Gtee Abuja, Nigeria

IT Assistant / Mid-Level Software Engineer 2020 – Till Date

M-TECH Computer Institute Gusau, Zamfara State

Centre Coordinator / Junior Software Engineer 2018 – 2020

Hossanah Cyber Café Jos, Plateau State

Intern / Computer Operator 2015 – 2016

EDUCATION

BSc. (Hons.) Zoology

University of Jos, Plateau State Nigeria 2016

TRAININGS AND CERTIFICATIONS

Blockchain Specialization Certificate

Coursera 2023

Cryptocurrency and Blockchain Course Certficate

Coursera

2023

Proficiency Certificate in Java Programming

PassionView Solution Gusau, Zamfara 2017

Diploma in Computer Studies

DataMaxx Computer Institute Jos, Plateau State 2015

PROFESSIONAL MEMBERSHIP

Chartered Member of Computer Professionals (Registration Council of Nigeria)

HOBBIES AND OTHER INTERESTS

Playing Chess Game, Travelling, Swimming, Biodiversity

REFEREES AVAILABLE UPON REQUEST